<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string name="app_name">Night Light</string>

    <string name="color_intensity">Filter Intensity</string>

    <string name="blue_color_intensity_desc">Intensity of the blue light to be filtered out. Higher value means higher intensity of blue light will be filtered out, lower value means lower intensity of blue light will be filtered out.</string>
    <string name="green_color_intensity_desc">Intensity of the green light to be filtered out. Here the range of control is limited. Filtering out green light will give a reddish tint to the screen.</string>

    <string name="master_switch">Enable Night Light</string>
    <string name="master_switch_desc">Master switch to enable/disable Night Light.</string>

    <string name="no_root_access">No root access</string>
    <string name="no_root_desc">Root access is needed for Night Light to work.</string>

    <string name="no_kcal">Incompatible</string>
    <string name="no_kcal_desc">Your kernel does not support KCAL. KCAL is a display driver tuning feature for Qualcomm devices. KCAL support is needed for Night Light to work.</string>

    <string name="auto_enable">Automatic switch</string>
    <string name="auto_enable_desc">Automatically enable Night Light between the specified time. Night Light will be automatically disabled outside this time range.</string>
    <string name="start_time">Start time</string>
    <string name="end_time">End time</string>

    <string name="start_time_default" translatable="false">00:00</string>
    <string name="end_time_default" translatable="false">06:00</string>

    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>

    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="app_desc">Night Light uses KCAL, which is a display driver tuning feature for new generation Qualcomm devices, to adjust the intensity of blue light, which makes it more comfortable for your eyes when you are using your phone in the dark and helps you fall asleep. Since it makes changes at driver level, and it does not use any software overlays, it is battery friendly and the change can be seen everywhere on the display.</string>

    <string name="shortcut_toggle">Toggle on/off</string>

    <string name="next_day">&#160;(Next day)</string>

    <string name="blue_light">Blue light</string>
    <string name="green_light">Green light</string>

    <string name="force_switch">Force Night Light</string>
    <string name="force_switch_desc">This will force enable/disable Night Light, disregarding the automatic schedule.</string>

    <string name="sun_switch">Use sunset/sunrise timings</string>

    <string name="location_unavailable">Unable to get your last known location.</string>

    <string name="like_this_app">Like this app?</string>
    <string name="get_donation">If you like this app, you can consider getting the donation version of the app. Although it comes with no extra features than this version, it shows your support and appreciation to the app, and it will motivate the developer and support the development of the app :)</string>
    <string name="kcal_preservce_value_msg">Preserve current KCAL values</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="contributors">Contributors</string>
    <string name="contributors_desc">Tap to see who else contributed to this project.</string>

    <string name="color_temperature_title">Color Temperature</string>
    <string name="color_temperature_desc">Value of the color temperature to be set. Lower temperatures are better suitable for low light viewing.</string>
    <string name="advanced_automation">Advanced automation</string>

    <string name="enabled">Enabled</string>
    <string name="disabled">Disabled</string>

    <string name="set_on_boot_delay_title">Set on boot delay</string>
    <string name="set_on_boot_delay_desc">Set the delay after which Night Light settings will be restored and applied after boot. Night Light settings will be applied after %s delay.</string>
    <string name="set_on_boot_delay_warn">Looks like Night Light settings were restored but could not be applied after most recent boot. Consider increasing this delay so that settings can be successfully restored and applied after boot.</string>

    <string name="suggest_enabling_automation">Please enable Automatic switch to use advanced automation features.</string>

    <string name="kcal_backup_set_title">KCAL backup settings</string>
    <string name="kcal_backup_set_desc">You can configure your old KCAL settings here. These settings will applied when night light is turned off.</string>
    <string name="red">Red</string>
    <string name="green">Green</string>
    <string name="blue">Blue</string>
    <string name="test">Test</string>
    <string name="kcal_backup_set"><u>Configure KCAL backup settings?</u></string>

    <string name="title_activity_advanced_automation">Advanced Automation</string>

    <string name="advanced_automation_switch">Enable advanced automation</string>
    <string name="advanced_automation_desc">This feature adjusts the Night Light colour temperature accordingly within the automatic time period.</string>
    <string name="temperature_settings">Color temperature settings</string>
    <string name="maximum_temperature_title">Maximum temperature</string>
    <string name="maximum_temperature_desc">Maximum temperature from which temperature will start scaling down. This temperature will be applied during the start of the schedule, and then it will gradually decrease. Lower temperatures are better suited for viewing at night.</string>
    <string name="minimum_temperature_title">Minimum temperature</string>
    <string name="minimum_temperature_desc">Minimum temperature which will be applied at the peak time of the schedule. This temperature must be lesser than the maximum temperature setting, as temperature settings will gradually scale down from maximum temperature setting.</string>
    <string name="time_interval">Time Interval</string>
    <string name="scale_down_period_title">Scale down period</string>
    <string name="scale_down_period_desc">Temperatures will gradually decrease during this period, and Night Light settings based on those temperatures will be applied at equal interval of times. This period will start scaling down from the maximum temperature setting and scale down until it reaches the minimum temperature setting.</string>
    <string name="peak_period_title">Peak period</string>
    <string name="peak_period_desc">Night Light settings will remain constant during this period of time. The value of colour temperature applied during this period is that of minimum color temperature.</string>
    <string name="scale_up_period_title">Scale up period</string>
    <string name="scale_up_period_desc">Temperatures will gradually increase during this period from minimum temperature to maximum temperature, and Night Light settings based on those temperatures will be applied at equal interval of times. These values are automatically calculated from scale down and peak time values.</string>
    <string name="scaling_interval_title">Scaling Interval</string>
    <string name="scaling_interval_desc">Choose the time interval for applying the new Night Light settings.</string>
    <string name="one_hour">1 hour</string>
    <string name="half_hour">30 minutes</string>
</resources>
