<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Night Light</string>
    <string name="banner_app_name" translatable="false">v%1$s</string>

    <string name="color_intensity">Filter Intensity</string>

    <string name="blue_color_intensity_desc">Intensity of the blue light to be filtered out. Higher value means higher intensity of blue light will be filtered out, lower value means lower intensity of blue light will be filtered out.</string>
    <string name="green_color_intensity_desc">Intensity of the green light to be filtered out. Here the range of control is limited. Filtering out green light will give a reddish tint to the screen.</string>

    <string name="master_switch">Enable Night Light</string>
    <string name="master_switch_desc">Master switch to enable/disable Night Light.</string>

    <string name="no_root_access">No root access</string>
    <string name="no_root_desc">Root access is needed for Night Light to work.</string>

    <string name="no_kcal">Incompatible</string>
    <string name="no_kcal_desc">Your kernel does not support KCAL. KCAL is a display driver tuning feature for Qualcomm devices. KCAL support is needed for Night Light to work.</string>

    <string name="auto_enable">Automatic switch</string>
    <string name="auto_enable_desc">Automatically enable Night Light between the specified time. Night Light will be automatically disabled outside this time range.</string>
    <string name="start_time">Start time</string>
    <string name="end_time">End time</string>

    <string name="start_time_default" translatable="false">00:00</string>
    <string name="end_time_default" translatable="false">06:00</string>

    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>

    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="app_desc">Night Light uses KCAL, which is a display driver tuning feature for new generation Qualcomm devices, to adjust the intensity of blue light, which makes it more comfortable for your eyes when you are using your phone in the dark and helps you fall asleep. Since it makes changes at driver level, and it does not use any software overlays, it is battery friendly and the change can be seen everywhere on the display.</string>

    <string name="shortcut_toggle">Toggle on/off</string>

    <string name="next_day">&#160;(Next day)</string>

    <string name="blue_light">Blue light</string>
    <string name="green_light">Green light</string>

    <string name="force_switch">Force Night Light</string>
    <string name="force_switch_desc">This will force enable/disable Night Light, disregarding the automatic schedule.</string>

    <string name="sun_switch">Use sunset/sunrise timings</string>

    <string name="location_unavailable">Unable to get your last known location.</string>

    <string name="like_this_app">Like this app?</string>
    <string name="get_donation">If you like this app, you can consider getting the donation version of the app. Although it comes with no extra features than this version, it shows your support and appreciation to the app, and it will motivate the developer and support the development of the app :)</string>
    <string name="kcal_preservce_value_msg">Preserve current KCAL values</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="contributors"><u>Contributors</u></string>
    <string name="contributors_desc">Tap to see who else contributed to this project.</string>

    <string name="color_temperature_title">Color Temperature</string>
    <string name="color_temperature_desc">Value of the color temperature to be set. Lower temperatures are better suitable for low light viewing.</string>

    <string name="set_on_boot_delay_title">Set on boot delay</string>
    <string name="set_on_boot_delay_desc">Set the delay after which Night Light settings will be restored and applied after boot. Night Light settings will be applied after %s delay.</string>
    <string name="set_on_boot_delay_warn">Looks like Night Light settings were restored but could not be applied after most recent boot. Consider increasing this delay so that settings can be successfully restored and applied after boot.</string>

    <string name="kcal_backup_set_title">KCAL backup settings</string>
    <string name="kcal_backup_set_desc">You can configure your old KCAL settings here. These settings will applied when night light is turned off.</string>
    <string name="red">Red</string>
    <string name="green">Green</string>
    <string name="blue">Blue</string>
    <string name="kcal_backup_set"><u>Configure KCAL backup settings?</u></string>

    <string name="profile_title">Profiles</string>
    <string name="profile_create_title">Create profile</string>
    <string name="profile_create_desc">Create a profile (collection of settings), which you can then apply it easily with one click, or use apps like Tasker apply it for you,</string>
    <string name="profile_edit_title">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="profile_edit_desc">Edit an existing profile</string>
    <string name="profile_setting_mode">Setting mode</string>
    <string name="profile_nl_switch">Night Light switch</string>
    <string name="profile_nl_setting_unavailable">Setting unavailable</string>
    <string name="profile_create_name">Profile name</string>
    <string name="profile_create_name_error">A profile with same name already exists, please try another name.</string>
    <string name="profile_empty_title">No profiles created</string>
    <string name="profile_empty_desc">Tap the + button to start setting up a profile</string>

    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>

    <string name="delete_details">Are you sure want to delete the %1$s profile?</string>

    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="tasker_confirm_selection">Are you sure you want use %1$s profile as a part of your Tasker plugin routine?</string>

    <string name="tasker_error_title">Night Light disabled</string>
    <string name="tasker_error_desc">To use tasker plugin, you must enable Master Switch first.</string>

    <string name="donate_title">Actions</string>
    <string name="donate_with_app">Rate this app in Play Store</string>
    <string name="donate_with_paypal">Get the donate version of this app</string>

    <string name="section_main">Master controls</string>
    <string name="section_color">Color controls</string>
    <string name="section_sob">Set on boot</string>
    <string name="section_auto">Automation</string>
    <string name="section_misc">Misc</string>
    <string name="section_profiles_list">List of profiles created</string>

    <string name="profiles_desc">Profiles are collection of settings which can be applied with one click, or let apps like Tasker apply it for you using the automation capabilities that they provide.</string>

    <string name="kcal_backup_every_time_before_enabling">Backup current KCAL values every time before Night Light is enabled</string>

    <string name="faq">F.A.Q</string>
    <string name="master_switch_function_question">What does the master switch do?</string>
    <string name="master_switch_function_answer">It basically controls all the functions of the app. If master switch is off, none of the functions will be enabled, and vice versa.</string>
    <string name="master_switch_exist_question">OK then why does master switch exist? We would have to enable master switch anyway to use the app.</string>
    <string name="master_switch_exist_answer">Since Night Light supports features like automation and set on boot, it is necessary for such switch to exist, so that such external requests can be dealt with accordingly. Imagine you have this app installed, but for some reason you don\'t use the app, if master switch was not present at all, a previously set automation schedule could still turn on Night Light.</string>
    <string name="kcal_backup_question">What does the KCAL backup options do?</string>
    <string name="kcal_backup_answer">This option takes account of the user\'s custom KCAL settings. So that while turning off Night Light, the app is able to restore user's settings.</string>
</resources>
